# Joseph Barber

jbarber.me

# **Professional Summary**

I am a games programmer with multiple years of professional experience working with Unity3d and C#. I am experienced using multiple different version control software including Git and Plastic SCM, and have experience using software management tools such as Jira, Confluence and Trello. I also have experience programming in other languages (in university and in my free time), including C, C++, python, lua and javascript.

# **Employment**

### 2018 - Current: Programmer, Just Add Water (Development) Ltd.

Implementing core gameplay features and mechanics, audio and design tools. Performing profiling and optimisation.

# **Experience**

### 2019 - Current: Sniper Elite VR

Implementing core gameplay features and mechanics, audio and design tools. Performing profiling and optimisation.

#### 2018 - 2019: Ice Ace Scrats Nutty Adventure

Working in a team of three core programmers, my main responsibilities included implementing game audio, core gameplay mechanics, design tools and profiling and optimisation.

#### Education

### 2015 - 2018: University of Suffolk

- BSc (Hons) Computer Games Programming First class with Honors.
- 2018 Computer Games Programming Student of the Year.

#### References

Available upon request.